tennispoint.com 2017-12-13

# Tennis Team Management :: Tennis League Management :: Tennis Tournament Management :: Tennis Team Management for USTA, ALTA, Flex Leagues at TennisPoint.com!

**Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated: July 11, 2016**

TennisPoint knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the TennisPoint website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**  
This Privacy Policy covers TennisPoint's treatment of personal information that TennisPoint gathers when you are on the TennisPoint website (the "Site") and when you use TennisPoint services (collectively the "Service").

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that TennisPoint does not own or control, or to individuals that TennisPoint does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information About Users Does TennisPoint Collect?**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us:  
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information we collect includes:  
* Registration: In order for you to use certain TennisPoint services, such as mannaging your tennis team, you must complete a registration form including your full name and email address.

* User Content: You may create your own tennis teams and publish your own own articles on the Service and comment on the articles of others (collectively your "User Content").

2\. Automatic Information:  
* We receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information whenever you interact with us. TennisPoint automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, TennisPoint cookie information, and the page you requested.

* TennisPoint may display a counter on any page indicating the total number of times that page has been viewed. This includes member profile pages.

* Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. TennisPoint cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies , how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. You may choose to disable or reject cookies when using the Service, but you may not be able to access some of TennisPoint's most attractive features.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). TennisPoint has no access to or control over these cookies.

* If you choose to provide posts from your blog via TennisPoint, we may ask you to paste confirmation code into the external template of your blog that communicates with us to authenticate the blog as an authorized feed and places a badge on your blog identifying you as a TennisPoint Affiliate.

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we may work with partners who use mobile SDKs, including the OneSignal Messaging SDK, to passively collect information (collectively, "SDK Information"), which generally helps us deliver personalized notifications. This data may also be used to identify you in a unique manner across other devices or browsers for the purposes of customizing ads or content. Depending on the permissions granted to this application, this information may include personally identifiable information (PII) including your e-mail address. This information may also include precise location (i.e. GPS-level data) or WiFi information, apps you have installed and enabled, and your mobile identifier (e.g., Android Advertising ID).

**Consumer Control & Opt-Out Options**

> a. Opting-out of OneSignal Push Notifications
> 
> You may in most cases opt out of receiving push notifications by going to your device "Settings" and clicking on "Notifications," and then changing those settings for some or all of the apps on your device. (Different device configurations, or updates to devices, may affect or change how these settings work.)
> 
> b. Opting Out of "Cross-App" Advertising on Mobile Devices
> 
> You can opt out of having your mobile advertising identifiers used for certain types of interest-based (also called "cross-app") mobile behavioral advertising, by accessing the "settings" on your Apple or Android mobile device, as follows: By opening the Google Settings app on your device, selecting Ads, and then selecting the option to opt-out of interest-based ads. (Different device configurations, or updates to devices, may affect or change how these settings work.)

**How Does TennisPoint Use My Information?**  
* Profile information: TennisPoint allows other users to browse your full name, playing stats and personal or company URL within your member profile should you provide this optional information.

* Social sharing of User Content: TennisPoint allows other users to browse articles that you have written, edited, or commented on or your playing stats. This information is made available via your member profile or within the article which you performed the action on. TennisPoint may choose to post this data on other site features in the future.

* Syndication: TennisPoint allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.

* API: TennisPoint may allow third parties access to all TennisPoint data that is already publicly available through TennisPoint.com through an application program interface that allows other programs to interact with the Site. TennisPoint will keep passwords and blog settings private.

* Traffic data: TennisPoint uses this traffic data, including information gathered from cookies, to help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze trends, research the market for our services, and administer the website.

**Will TennisPoint Share Any of the Information it Receives?**  
We will not rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below.

* Providing the TennisPoint Service: TennisPoint personnel may have access to user information while carrying out their duties in the normal course of TennisPoint business. TennisPoint may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of TennisPoint (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

* Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in our Privacy Policy.

* Protection of TennisPoint and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of TennisPoint, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

* With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out.

**Is Information About Me Secure?**  
* Your TennisPoint account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information.

* Only TennisPoint employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

* TennisPoint uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to TennisPoint and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, TennisPoint makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. This information includes your User Content. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.

**What Information Can I Access?**  
You can access your personal information on our website and correct, amend, or delete information that is inaccurate by visiting your user profile setting page.

**What Choices Do I Have?**  
* You can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website.

* You can choose to disable or reject cookies from the Service, but you may not then be able to access many features of TennisPoint.

* You can add or update certain information on pages of the Site. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

* You may request deletion of your TennisPoint account by emailing us at support at tennispoint dot com.

**Can Children Use TennisPoint's Services?**  
You must be at least 13 years or older to register to use the TennisPoint website. Children between the age of 13 and 18 must have parental consent to register. TennisPoint does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on TennisPoint. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy at tennispoint dot com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
TennisPoint may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at our sole discretion. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the TennisPoint website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

**Questions?**  
Please e-mail privacy at tennispoint dot com
